{
    "subject": "resource/Damn_Seagulls",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Rock_music",
    "human_readable": "Damn Seagulls' genre is Rock music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9713295698165894,
            "question": "Is Damn Seagulls a Rock band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962416410446167,
            "question": "Are Damn Seagulls considered a Rock band by genre classification?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9566871523857117,
            "question": "Name a musical genre associated with Damn Seagulls."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9298540949821472,
            "question": "Describe the musical style of Damn Seagulls."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169563055038452,
            "question": "What genre of music does Damn Seagulls play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8984246253967285,
            "question": "To which music genre does Damn Seagulls belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8930075168609619,
            "question": "What type of music is performed by Damn Seagulls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572303652763367,
            "question": "If you wanted to hear Rock music, would you listen to Damn Seagulls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8165820837020874,
            "question": "What musical category defines Damn Seagulls' sound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8089103102684021,
            "question": "What kind of music do Damn Seagulls create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Damn Seagulls' genre is Rock music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2172_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical category defines Damn Seagulls' sound?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2172_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to hear Rock music, would you listen to Damn Seagulls?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2172_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music is performed by Damn Seagulls?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2172_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2172_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe text describes Damn Seagulls as a rock and alternative rock band, and mentions their albums and songs within these genres. The information supports the triple that Damn Seagulls' genre is Rock music."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the band Damn Seagulls, including their genre as rock and alternative rock. Therefore, the statement that Damn Seagulls' genre is rock music is supported by the context information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}